A Guide to the Records of the Division of Outreach and International Affairs, Sahel Regional Financial Management Project, 1982-1986
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Mauritania
  - Mauritania (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Mauritania; Agreements (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Mauritania; Cables (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Mauritania; Certification (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Mauritania; Correspondence - Incoming (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Mauritania; Correspondence - Outgoing (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Mauritania; General Information and Maps (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Mauritania; Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Interim Assessment of the Status of Assignment Tasks (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Mauritania Project Title II Section 206 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Mauritania - Reports; Annual Budget Submission FY, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Mauritania - Reports; Country Development Strategy Statement FY, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Mauritania - Reports and Publications; Baranson Consultancy, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Mauritania - Reports and Publications; Baranson Consultancy, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Mauritania - Reports and Publications; Libiszowski Consultancy, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Mauritania - Reports and Publications; Report on Cooperating Institutions (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Mauritania - Reports and Publications; Survey Report, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Niger
  - Niger (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Niger; Agreements (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Niger; Cables (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Niger; Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Niger; Correspondence - Incoming (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Niger - Publications; L'Audit de Projects (Boucher) (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Niger - Publications; MOP and USAID ACCTG and Reptapratues Counterpart Funds (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Niger - Publications; Pratique de la Comptabilite des Buns et Matieres (Dacosta) (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Niger - Publications; Rapport D'Activites sur L'Assistance AU Project de Plantification et Utilization (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Niger - Publications; Rapport sur le Seminaire de Gestion des Fonds Locaux a Namaro (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Niger - Publications; Requementatron Niger Lenne en Matiene D'approvisionnement Resume et Decrets (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Niger - Publications; SRFMP/Niger Work Plans and Budget, 1983-05-1985-09 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Niger Correspondence - Outgoing (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Niger Certification (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Niger Financial Management Guidelines (USAID/N) (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Niger General Information and Maps (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Niger Leases (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Niger Telexes - Incoming (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Niger Telexes - Outgoing (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Niger Reports Annual Budject Submission - FY, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Niger Reports Final Report: "Financial Management Improvement Efforts in Niger from 5/83 to 5/85" by Bruneau, 1983-1985 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Niger - Reports; Trip Reports (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Niger - Reports; Tshibanda (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Niger - Sahel Regional Financial Management Project (SRFMP); Budgets (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Niger - SRFMP; Evaluation (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Niger - SRFMP; Progress Reports (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Niger - SRFMP; Work Plan (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Niger - Publications; Assistance Au Project Gestion des Paturages, Tahoua (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Niger - Publications; Basic ACCTG for USAID PD, PO, and PA (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Niger Collection of Materials produced during Consultation 1984 - Lusby, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Niger - Publications; Compte Rendu de L'atelier de Travail sur L'Approvisionnement et lat Gestion des... (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Niger - Inventory Mgmt Outline - Lusby (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Senegal
  - Senegalese Accounting Plan (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Seminaire Sur la Gestion des Projets, 1985-07 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Prealablement a la Mise en Place de Manuel de Procedure (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Seminaire Sur la Gestion des Projets de Programme PL 480 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Seminaire de Gestion de Projets, 1985-07-12 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Rapport sur le Seminaire, 1985-07 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Sahel Manpower Development Project (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Senegal Agreements (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Senegal Cables (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Senegal Certification (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Senegal: SRFMP Evaluation (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Senegal Correspondence - Incoming, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Senegal Correspondence - Incoming (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Senegal Correspondence - Outgoing (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Senegal General Information and Maps (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Senegal Telexes (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Senegal Reports; Annual Budget Submission FY, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Senegal An Overview of the Current USAID Program in Senegal, 1982-02 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Senegal Reports; Procedures Manual (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Senegal Reports; Seminar on Project Management, 1985-07-01-1985-07-03 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Senegal Reports; Country Development Strategy Statement FY, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Senegal Rural Health II Project - Money (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Senegal Project Accounts (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Senegal Reports; Trip Reports (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Senegal SRFMP; Newsletters (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Senegal SRFMP; Budget (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Senegal SRFMP; Personnel (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Senegal SRFMP; Progress Reports (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Senegal SRFMP; Work Plans (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Senegal Publications; Basic Accounting System designed for Project PL 480 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Senegal Publications; Information on Plan Combrable Senegalais (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Senegal Publications; Les Institutions De Prevogance Maladei Au Senegai: Problemes de Gestion el Perspect (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Senegal Publications; Draft DMVS accounting and Administration Procedures Manual (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Senegal Publications; PIDAC Plan (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Senegal (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Senegal; Audit Reports, Internal Control Vulnerability Assessment (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Senegal; General Papers (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Upper Volta / Burkina Faso
  - Upper Volta (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Upper Volta Agreements (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Upper Volta Audit Reports; Internal Control Vulnerability Assessment (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Upper Volta Cables (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Upper Volta Certification (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Upper Volta Correspondence - Incoming (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Upper Volta Correspondence - Outgoing (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Upper Volta Project Evaluation (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Upper Volta General Information and Maps (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Upper Volta - Leases (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Upper Volta - Miscellaneous (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Burkina Faso Telexes (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Upper Volta Reports; Annual Budget Submission - FY, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Upper Volta Reports; From Fund Accounting to Financial and Project Management (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Upper Volta Reports; Trip Reports (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Upper Volta SRFMP; Budget (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Upper Volta SRFMP; Monthly Reports (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Upper Volta SRFMP; Personnel (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Upper Volta SRFMP; Procedures (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Upper Volta Work Plan (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Personnel
  - Agency for International Development (AID) Handbook: Overseas Support (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - General - Telexes Incoming (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Personnel - Short Term Consultants, Financial Management (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Personnel - Short Term Consultants Candidates, Auditing (French) (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - General - Chron; Incoming continued, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Chron File Incoming - Folder 1 of 4, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Chron File Incoming - Folder 2 of 4, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Chron File Incoming - Folder 3 of 4, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Chron File Incoming - Folder 4 of 4, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Personnel - VA Tech Faculty in Dept. of Accounting (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Personnel/Orientation Front Royal Workshop (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Budget and Funding, 1984-08-1984-11 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Budget and Funding, 1984-06-1984-08 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Budget and Funding, 1982-11-1984-05 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Orientation - FSI Testing (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - General - Country Team Leader Organization (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Orientation - Virginia Tech Seminar, 1983-06-27 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Personnel; Short-Term Consultants, Michel C. Bagbonon (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Personnel; Sahel Project Consultants (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Personnel; Short-Term Consultants, Stanly Baranson (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Personnel; Short-Term Consultants, Claire Boucher (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Personnel; Short-Term Consultants, Suzanne Brunstein (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Personnel; Short-Term Consultants, Charles Christian (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Personnel; Short-Term Consultants, Pio Da Costa (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Personnel; Short-Term Consultants, Michael Halus (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Personnel; Short-Term Consultants, Leo Herbert (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Personnel; Short-Term Consultants, Mildred A. Konan (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Personnel; Short-Term Consultants, John Larocca (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Personnel; Short-Term Consultants, William Le Clere (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Personnel; Short-Term Consultants, Thomas C. Leonhardt (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Personnel; Short-Term Consultants, David B. Levine (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Personnel; Short-Term Consultants, Frank Lusby (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Personnel; Short-Term Consultants, Paul C. Libiszowski (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Personnel; Short-Term Consultants, Christophe T. de Montalte (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Personnel; Short-Term Consultants, Gilda Nachman (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Personnel; Short-Term Consultants, William M. O'Reilly (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Personnel; Short-Term Consultants, Patricia Perkins (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Personnel; Short-Term Consultants, Gene Peuse (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Personnel; Short-Term Consultants, Ronald Phillips (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Personnel; Short-Term Consultants, Mary Pat Rafferty (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Personnel; Short-Term Consultants, Vernon D. Razak (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Personnel; Short-Term Consultants, Christopher Ritzert (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Personnel; Short-Term Consultants, Nelson M. Robinson (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Personnel; Short-Term Consultants, Robert Roussel (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Personnel; Short-Term Consultants, Albert Sour (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Personnel; Short-Term Consultants, Robert K. Spears (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Personnel; Short-Term Consultants, Sandra Travis (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Personnel; Short-Term Consultants, Janet Tuthill (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Personnel; Short-Term Consultants, Myron Woolman (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Personnel; Short-Term Consultants, David I. Yohalem (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Consultant Report - General; Team Planning Meeting (TPM) for Evaluation Team - Michael B. Halus (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Consultant Report - General; Mary P. Rafferty (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Publications and Reports - SRFMP; Model Conference Documentation - Travis, 1984-06-04-1984-06-08 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Consultant Report - General; Management Evaluation System (MES) Myron Woolman, 1983-04-14 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Evaluations (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Assessment and Evaluation Forms (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Budget and Funding Folder 1 of 2, 1985-07-1985-09 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Budget and Funding Folder 2 of 2, 1985-10-1985-12 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Personnel; Faulkner (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Personnel; J. P. Raleigh - Final Report (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Personnel; Werner, Richard (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Personnel; Walker (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Personnel; Williams (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Personnel; Employees Handbooks - VA Tech (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Personnel; General Correspondence (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Personnel; Organizational Chart - SRFMP (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Personnel; Policy Consultants (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Personnel; Recruitment (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Personnel; Recruitment, Country Team Leader Sample Packet (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Personnel; Selection, Country Team Leader Selection Process (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - SRFMP; Training Officer's Reports, 1985-04-16 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- Correspondence
  - Outgoing Correspondence
    - Chron File; Outgoing cont., Folder 1 of 4, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Chron File; Outgoing cont., Folder 2 of 4, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Chron File; Outgoing cont., Folder 3 of 4, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Chron File; Outgoing cont., Folder 4 of 4, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Chron File; Outgoing, Folder 1 of 4, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Chron File; Outgoing, Folder 2 of 4, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Chron File; Outgoing, Folder 3 of 4, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Chron File; Outgoing, Folder 4 of 4, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Chron File; Outgoing, Folder 1 of 3, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Chron File; Outgoing, Folder 2 of 3, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Chron File; Outgoing, Folder 3 of 3, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - General; Telexes - Outgoing, Folder 1 of 4 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - General; Telexes - Outgoing, Folder 2 of 4 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - General; Telexes - Outgoing, Folder 3 of 4 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - General; Telexes - Outgoing, Folder 4 of 4 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Chron File; Outgoing, Folder 1 of 2, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Chron File; Outgoing, Folder 2 of 2, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Chron File; Outgoing, Folder 1 of 8, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Chron File; Outgoing, Folder 2 of 8, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Chron File; Outgoing, Folder 3 of 8, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Chron File; Outgoing, Folder 4 of 8, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Chron File; Outgoing, Folder 5 of 8, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Chron File; Outgoing, Folder 6 of 8, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Chron File; Outgoing, Folder 7 of 8, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Chron File; Outgoing, Folder 8 of 8, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Chron File; Outgoing, Folder 1 of 4, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Chron File; Outgoing, Folder 2 of 4, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Chron File; Outgoing, Folder 3 of 4, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Chron File; Outgoing, Folder 4 of 4, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Incoming Correspondence
    - Chron FIle; Incoming, Folder 1 of 3, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Chron FIle; Incoming, Folder 2 of 3, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Chron FIle; Incoming, Folder 3 of 3, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Chron File; Incoming, Folder 1 of 3, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Chron File; Incoming, Folder 2 of 3, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Chron File; Incoming, Folder 3 of 3, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Chron File; Incoming, Folder 1 of 5, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Chron File; Incoming, Folder 2 of 5, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Chron File; Incoming, Folder 3 of 5, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Chron File; Incoming, Folder 4 of 5, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Chron File; Incoming, Folder 5 of 5, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Chron File; Incoming, Folder 1 of 4, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Chron File; Incoming, Folder 2 of 4, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Chron File; Incoming, Folder 3 of 4, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Chron File; Incoming, Folder 4 of 4, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Publications
  - Reports and Pubs - SRFMP; The SRFMP Management Information System (MIS) - French, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Reports and Pubs - SRFMP; SRFMP MIS - Portuguese, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Reports and Pubs - SRFMP; SRFMP MIS, Folder 1 of 3 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Reports and Pubs - SRFMP; SRFMP MIS, Folder 2 of 3 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Reports and Pubs - SRFMP; SRFMP MIS, Folder 3 of 3 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Reports and Pubs; "The Sahel Financial Improvement Effort, 1981-1982", 1983-05 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Reports and Pubs; "Training and Related Efforts Needed to Improve Financial Management in the Third World", 1979-09-20 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Reports and Pubs; Training Guide for USAID Projects, 1977-12 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Reports and Pubs; "United States Code (Income Tax for US Contractor Hire)", 1981 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Reports and Pubs; US Accounting and the Third World (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Reports and Pubs; USDA International Technical Assistance, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Reports and Pubs; User's Manual for Basic Accounting System - Drafts and Previous Versions, 1981-09-03 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Reports and Pubs; User's Manual for Basic Accounting (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - FMIT - Project Site Visits; Checklist/Report Forms (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - FMIT - Club du Sahel (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - FMIT - Sahel; General, 1983-05 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - FMIT - Cape Verde (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - FMIT - The Gambia (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - FMIT - Guinea/Bissau (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - FMIT - Mali (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - FMIT - Mali, Documentation from Workshop (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - FMIT - Mauritania (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - FMIT - Niger (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - FMIT - Niger, Documentation from Workshop (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - FMIT - Senegal (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - FMIT - Upper Volta (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Development Project Management Center (DPMC) Handbook (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Accounting Workshop Simulation Packets (English)
    Scope and Contents
    Adapted by Perkins and Robinson from the French for use in the Gambia
    - Accounting Workshop Simulation Packets - Simulation 1 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Accounting Workshop Simulation Packets - Simulation 2 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Accounting Workshop Simulation Packets - Simulation 3 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Accounting Workshop Simulation Packets - Simulation 4 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Accounting Workshop Simulation Packets - Simulation 5 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Accounting Workshop Simulation Packets - Simulation 6 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Accounting Workshop Simulation Packets - Simulation 7 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Accounting Workshop Simulation Packets - Simulation 8 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Accounting Workshop Simulation Packets - Simulation 9 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Sahel General and FMIT (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Reports and Pubs; "Action-Training In Project Planning and Management" - Kettering, 1976-1979 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Reports and Pubs; "An Action-Training Strategy for Project Management" (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Reports and Pubs; The Administrative and Financial Practice of the Safgrad Project Needs to be Improved, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Reports and Pubs; Africa Beset (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Reports and Pubs; An Approach to a Research Methodology Leading to Country Assistance Reports, 1983-12 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Reports and Pubs; An Approach to Evaluation of Financial Management, 1984-09 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Reports and Pubs; Applying Project Implementation Monitoring and Accelerated Learning, 1982-05 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Reports and Pubs; Assessment of Sahel Development Program, 1983-03 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Reports and Pubs; Auditor Training Courses - Canadian, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Reports and Pubs; Draft Audit Report on "Agriculture Credit Programs in the Sahel", 1983 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Reports and Pubs; "The Budget Calendar in Lesotho" (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Reports and Pubs; "Bureaucratic Politics and Incentives in the Management of Rural Development" (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Reports and Pubs; "Comite permanent Interetats de Lutte contre la Secheresse dans le Sahel (CILSS)" (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Reports and Pubs; Development Assistance Program Sahel Development Program (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Reports and Pubs; Economic Development Institute (EDI) Course Notes Series (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Reports and Pubs; Essentials for the Scientific and Technical Writer (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Reports and Pubs; "Financial and Program Management in the Sahel: Assessing the Potential of Local Resources Involvement", 1982-06 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Reports and Pubs; Fund Accounting System (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Reports and Pubs; Government Accounting in Economic Development Management (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Reports and Pubs; "Guidelines for Internal Audit" (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Reports and Pubs; Inter-American Institute for Cooperation on Agriculture(IICA)-Proplan/United States Department of Agriculture(USDA)-DPMC Seminar, 1981-12-06-1981-12-09 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Reports and Pubs; "Implementing Project Management Information Systems in USAID Missions", 1984-01 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Reports and Pubs; Improving Financial Accountability and Financial Management in the Sahel (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Reports and Pubs; Improving Financial and Program Management (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Reports and Pubs; International Consortium of Governmental Financial management, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Reports and Pubs;International Federation of Accountants, 1984-11 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Reports and Pubs; "Introduction to the Financial Management Effort in the Sahel", 1982-01 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Reports and Pubs; A Manual for Government Accounting (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Cost/Business Management Proposal, 1986-01-31 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence; VPI and SU (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence; General (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - VPI and SU; Recruiting/Admissions Guidelines (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - VPI and SU; Extension Division Advisory Activity Report Summary (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Tech; Internal Evaluation Materials provided to Pinnock/Wise, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Tech; Internal Evaluation Materials provided to Pinnock/Wise, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Report on Interim Evaluation of SRFMP, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - VPI and SU; Internal Evaluation Instruments: SRFMP, 1984-04-1984-05 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Evaluation; General (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Evaluation; MIS Miscellaneous Information (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Evaluation; Scope of Work for Evaluation of SRFMP, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Evaluation; Scope of Work for Evaluation of SRFMP, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - USDA/OICS/VPI and SU Agreement, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - USDA/OICS/VPI and SU Agreement, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - USDA/OICS/VPI and SU Agreement Correspondence (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - General; AID Standard Lease Form (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - General; DPMC Monthly Reports (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - General; News Articles on Africa (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - General; Closeout (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - General; Executive Summary (Draft) (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - General; Final Report Draft (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - General; Final Project Report (Instructions) (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - General; Final Project Report, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - General; Final Project Report, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - General; Regional Meeting, 1983-10 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Regional Conference - Abidjan, 1984-12 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Reports and Pubs; Manual for Project Accounting - Deutsche Gesellschaft für Technische Zusammenarbeit (GTZ) (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Reports and Pubs; Manual on Economic Development Projects (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Reports and Pubs; Manual Practico Sistema Contabil Simplificado (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Reports and Pubs; Manuel practique systeme comptable simplifie (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Reports and Pubs; "Microcomputers and Agriculture Management in Developing Countries" (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Reports and Pubs; Mid-Term Evaluation (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Reports and Pubs; Multifaceted Action-training approach for improving project management (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Reports and Pubs; "Plan Comptable General des Entreprises" (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Reports and Pubs; Planning in Developing Countries (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Reports and Pubs; A Practical Manual for a Simplified Accounting System (Box 24, Folder 10)